{
    "subject": "Ali_Selim",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Sweet_Land",
    "human_readable": "Ali Selim created Sweet Land.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9039843082427979,
            "question": "Is Ali Selim known for creating other things besides Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.71612548828125,
            "question": "Who created Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6448516845703125,
            "question": "What did Ali Selim make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6016107201576233,
            "question": "What is the name of the creation by Ali Selim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3498489260673523,
            "question": "What kind of thing is Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3455463945865631,
            "question": "What is the purpose of Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24224720895290375,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23503290116786957,
            "question": "Who might be interested in learning about Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22612178325653076,
            "question": "Where can I learn more about Sweet Land?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13085545599460602,
            "question": "Is Sweet Land a book, movie, or something else?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ali Selim created Sweet Land.",
            "html": "yago_12095_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I learn more about Sweet Land?",
            "html": "yago_12095_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might be interested in learning about Sweet Land?",
            "html": "yago_12095_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Sweet Land?",
            "html": "yago_12095_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12095_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the information in the documents supports the triple, and Ali Selim did create Sweet Land. This is confirmed by multiple documents mentioning Ali Selim as the writer-director of the film Sweet Land."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Sweet Land\" and its creator, Ali Selim. For example, from the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12095/re-ranker-msmarco/4.txt`, it is mentioned that \"Sweet Land (2005) is a feature-length movie created by Ali Selim.\" This supports the statement that Ali Selim created Sweet Land."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}